ripmax.com 2019-01-10

# Ripmax Privacy Policy

**General Overview**  
Ripmax Ltd, the operator of this website, respects the privacy of every individual who visits this site. Our Privacy Policy is designed to explain the way we use and disclose any personal information that you provide to us whilst visiting the site. Personal information includes any information that identifies you personally, such as your name, address or email address. 

**Sharing data**  
Other than as set out in this Privacy Policy, Ripmax will not disclose, rent or sell your personal information to any third party unrelated to us without your prior permission, other than as required by law. Any personal information which you provide to us is held in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulations (released in 2018).

**GDPR - General Data Protection Regulations**  
GDPR stands for 'General Data Protection Regulations'. This was implemented by the EU and UK government to protect the data you supply to companies from misuse. Here at Ripmax we take this very seriously and have taken steps to log and secure our customers data.

  1. Informed - This means you have the right to request a copy of the data we have related to you.
  2. Rectification - You have the right to correct inaccurate data and/or incomplete data.
  3. Restrict Processing - In some cases you have the right to restrict the processing of personal data, for example if you contest the accuracy or need the data kept for legal reasons but no longer need our services.
  4. Erasure - You have the right to request we delete data that is no longer relevant.
  5. Portability - You have the right to request you data in a readable format for you to reuse.
  6. Right to complain - You have the right to complain to a supervisory authority.
  7. Withdraw Consent - You can withdraw your consent to use the supplied data once it is no longer needed.

For an in depth overview of the GDPR regulations and what your rights are please visit the ICO (Information Commissioner's Office) at [www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/)

**Google Analytics**  
This website uses the Google Analytics to track usage, as a result reports can be produced that contain statements on the age, gender and interests of the site visitors. This data comes from interest-based advertising from Google and third-party visitor data. This data can not be assigned to a specific person. You can disable this feature at any time through the ad settings in your Google Account, or generally prohibit the collection of your data by Google Analytics. Google is located at Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA.

For more information on how to handle user data on Google Analytics, please refer to the Google Privacy Policy: <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en>

**YouTube**  
Our website uses plugins from the Google-powered YouTube video sharing website. The site operator is YouTube, LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA. When you visit one of our YouTube plug-in-enabled pages, you will be connected to the servers of YouTube and this tells the YouTube server which of our pages you've visited. If you're logged into your YouTube account, YouTube will allow you to associate your browsing behaviour directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account.

For more information about how to handle user data, please refer to the YouTube Privacy Policy at <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy>.

**Data Security**  
We ensure that all reasonable steps are taken to protect your personal information. All the data collected by us is stored on a secure server however we cannot guarantee that any data sent over the internet is completely secure.

**Contact Details**  
Address: Ripmax Ltd, 241 Green Street, Enfield, EN3 7SJ United Kingdom  
Email: [sales@ripmax.com](mailto:sales@ripmax.com)  
Phone: 0208 282 7500  
Public Website: [http://www.ripmax.com](http://www.ripmax.com/)  
Trade Website: [http://trade1.ripmax.com](http://trade1.ripmax.com/)
